Steven J. Cobilich

IMMERSIVE SOUND DESIGNER - FREELANCE AUDIO ENGINEER

7449 West Manchester Ave Los Angeles, Ca 90045 (818) 984-4217 steven@1six1group.com

ABOUT ME

I am an audio system designer and engineer with experience as a project manager and operator for new facility infrastructure, theatrical and concert performances with interest in immersive installations. I am very passionate about always providing a world-class acoustic environment and exploring the capabilities of storytelling through sound. Since my childhood experiences at Disneyland, I have always been captivated by the potential of spatial audio and immersive environments. After four years of military service and then almost ten years of experience working in concert touring and festival sound, I am about to enter my third year at the California Institute of the Arts, where I am currently finishing my bachelor's degree in Experience Design and Production Sound Design and working on my Avixa certs.

CERTS & SKILLS

Certifications:	Classes:	Skills:	
L'Acoustics; K1, K2, VCLS, SV and SF	SMAART/M1/P1	Sound Design	Audio System Design
Pro Tools 101	Vectorworks	AVB	FOH/MON Engineer
QSC Q-SYS lvl 1	Sketchup	Ableton Live	Project Management
Dante Levels 1-3	Fusion360	QLab	PS/AI

EXPERIENCE

1.61 Productions — System Design and FOH

MAY2010 - Present

Served as a system designer and operator through my DBA 1.61 PRO for a number of events, tours, and installations. Clients/events include; Sound Factory Systems/Insomniac (edc), , Rat Sound/Live Nation (Fonda), SpaceLand(Echo/Echoplex). Tours include: 88Rising(FOH), Warped Tour(FOH). Artists include: DeadMau5, Coolio, Carl Cox Etc. Full List with details upon request. (Ref; Adam Figeroua - Rat Sound Systems , Auggie Esquivel - Sound Factory Systems)

Warner Music Group, — FOH Engineer, Asst Prod Manager (freelance)

JAN2018 - Present

Served as front of house engineer and assistant PM, operating and assisting with the advancment of shows for in house events and showcases with label artists and upper management. Provided oversight and commissioning for a new audio system installation. (Ref; Chris Costello - PM WMG)

EDUCATION

California Institute of the Arts, Valencia, CA — Bachelor of Fine Arts

Experience Design and Production

AUG2020 - MAY2024 (In progress)

Experience Design and Production, with a focus in Immersive Sound Design and Themed Entertainment. Studied the history, present and future of themed/narrative environments, while practicing and studying advanced sound design, music production, and theatrical design techniques, including various pre-vis and computer aided design softwares. Provided sound design for various MFA productions, including The Fig and The Wasp (dir. Josh Sobel) and Obsession (dir. Peng Hsu)

Los Angeles Recording School, Hollywood, CA — (12 Month Course)

Recording Technology

AUG2010 - AUG2011

Learned the fundamentals of recording technology, live sound and the music business in general.